http://www.dict8.com/privacypolicy

NHS Budget Cuts
Why should you outsource your medical transcription?
Case study: Article from the The British Society for Human Genetics
Case study: Dictation versus Template Systems in the Emergency Room
Article: Patient anxiety and waiting
Article: Outsourcing doesn't have to be offshore!
NHS Budget Cuts
Why should you outsource your medical transcription?
Case study: Article from the The British Society for Human Genetics
Case study: Dictation versus Template Systems in the Emergency Room
Article: Patient anxiety and waiting
Article: Outsourcing doesn't have to be offshore!
Customer Testimonials
Type for us
Privacy policy & cookies DICT8 Limited understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used. We respect and value the privacy of everyone who visits our websites, which include dict8.com, dict8help.com, dict8support.com and dict8login.com, and will only collect and use personal data in ways that are described here, and in a way that is consistent with our obligations and your rights under the law.Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and ensure that you understand it. Your acceptance of this Privacy Policy is deemed to occur upon your first use of any of our Sites. If you do not accept and agree with this Privacy Policy, you must stop using Our Sites immediately.1. Definitions and Interpretation In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings:  “Account”means an account required to access and/or use certain areas and features of Our Sites;“Cookie”means a small text file placed on your computer or device by Our Sites when you visit certain parts of Our Sites and/or when you use certain features of Our Sites. Details of the Cookies used by Our Sites are set out in Part 14, below; and“Cookie Law”means the relevant parts of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003;2. Information About UsOur Sites are owned and operated by DICT8 Limited, a Limited company registered in England under company number 478116592.Main trading address: 1A St Mary Abbots Place, London W8 6Ls3. What Does This Policy Cover?This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of Our Sites. Our Sites may contain links to other websites. Please note that we have no control over how your data is collected, stored, or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.4. What is Personal Data?Personal data is defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (EU Regulation 2016/679) (the “GDPR”) as ‘any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier’.Personal data is, in simpler terms, any information about you that enables you to be identified. Personal data covers obvious information such as your name and contact details, but it also covers less obvious information such as identification numbers, electronic location data, and other online identifiers.5. What Are My Rights?Under the GDPR, you have the following rights, which we will always work to uphold:a)            The right to be informed about our collection and use of your personal data. This Privacy Policy should tell you everything you need to know, but you can always contact us to find out more or to ask any questions using the details in Part 15.b)            The right to access the personal data we hold about you. Part 13 will tell you how to do this.c)             The right to have your personal data rectified if any of your personal data held by is inaccurate or incomplete. Please contact us using the details in Part 15 to find out more.d)            The right to be forgotten. Please contact us using the details in Part 15 to find out more.e)            The right to restrict (i.e. prevent) the processing of your personal data.f)              The right to object to us using your personal data for a particular purpose or purposes.g)            The right to data portability. This means that, if you have provided personal data to us directly, we are using it with your consent or for the performance of a contract, and that data is processed using automated means, you can ask us for a copy of that personal data to re-use with another service or business in certain cases.For more information about our use of your personal data or exercising your rights as outlined above, please contact us using the details provided in Part 15.Further information about your rights can also be obtained from the Information Commissioner’s Office or your local Citizens Advice Bureau.If you have any cause for complaint about our use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.6. What Data Do We Collect?Depending upon your use of Our Site, we may collect some or all of the following personal and non-personal data (please also see Part 14 on our use of Cookies and similar technologies).Name;Date of birth;Address;Email address;Telephone number;Business name;Job title;Profession;IP address;Web browser type and version;Operating system;Working history.Other data as may be required for the provision our services to you.7. How Do You Use My Personal Data?Under the GDPR, we must always have a lawful basis for using personal data. This may be because the data is necessary for our performance of a contract with you, because you have consented to our use of your personal data, or because it is in our legitimate business interests to use it. Your personal data may be used for the following purposes:Providing and managing your Account;Providing and managing your access to Our Sites;Personalising and tailoring your experience on Our Sites;Supplying our products and services to you. Your personal details are required in order for us to enter into a contract with you.Personalising and tailoring our products and services for you.Communicating with you. This may include responding to emails or calls from you.Supplying you with information by email, phone and post, by sending us a request through our online form or by creating an account on the system you are agreeing to opt in to be sent information that relates to either the request that you have made or your account (you may unsubscribe or opt-out at any time by contacting by email). We will not send you information that is irrelevant to this.Analysing your use of Our Sites and gathering feedback to enable us to continually improve Our Sites and your user experience.To ensure the security of data uploaded to Our Sites and to ensure that we have full records of all that have interacted with it.To comply with any and all laws and regulations as well as reducing fraud or any other improper behaviour.We use certain automated systems for carrying out certain kinds of decision-making and profiling. If at any point you wish to query any action that we take on the basis of this or wish to request ‘human intervention’ (i.e. have someone review the action themselves, rather than relying only on the automated method), the GDPR gives you the right to do so. Please contact us to find out more using the details in Part 15.8. How Long Will You Keep My Personal Data?We will not keep your personal data for any longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected. 9. How and Where Do You Store or Transfer My Personal Data?We will only store or transfer your personal data in the UK. This means that it will be fully protected under the GDPR.10. Do You Share My Personal Data?We will not share your personal data with any third parties for any purposes, other than in the following cases: In some limited circumstances, we may be required to share certain personal data, which might include yours, if we are involved in legal proceedings or complying with legal obligations, a court order, or the instructions of a government authority. We may also be required to share details when asked to do so by clients or customers of Ours as part of an investigation into improper use of, or access to, data or where they suspect fraud or other improper behaviour.Where we integrate with, or link to, another system, certain data may be shared for the proper execution of Our business.We may share your personal data with other companies in our group for conduct of our business. 11. How Can I Control My Personal Data?In addition to your rights under the GDPR, set out in Part 5, when you submit personal data via Our Sites, you may be given options to restrict our use of your personal data.  You may also wish to sign up to one or more of the preference services operating in the UK: The Telephone Preference Service (“the TPS”), the Corporate Telephone Preference Service (“the CTPS”), and the Mailing Preference Service (“the MPS”). These may help to prevent you receiving unsolicited marketing. Please note, however, that these services will not prevent you from receiving marketing communications that you have consented to receiving.12. Can I Withhold Information?You may access certain areas of Our Sites without providing any personal data at all. However, to use all features and functions available on Our Sites you may be required to submit or allow for the collection of certain data.13. How Can I Access My Personal Data?If you want to know what personal data we have about you, you can ask us for details of that personal data and for a copy of it (where any such personal data is held). This is known as a “subject access request”.All subject access requests should be made in writing and sent to the email or postal addresses shown in Part 15. There is not normally any charge for a subject access request. If your request is ‘manifestly unfounded or excessive’ (for example, if you make repetitive requests) a fee may be charged to cover our administrative costs in responding.We will respond to your subject access request within 30 days and, in any case, not more than one month of receiving it. Normally, we aim to provide a complete response, including a copy of your personal data within that time. In some cases, however, particularly if your request is more complex, more time may be required up to a maximum of three months from the date we receive your request. You will be kept fully informed of our progress.14. How Do You Use Cookies?Our Sites may place and access certain first-party Cookies on your computer or device. First-party Cookies are those placed directly by us and are used only by us. We use Cookies to facilitate and improve your experience of Our Sites and to provide and improve our products and services. We have carefully chosen these Cookies and have taken steps to ensure that your privacy and personal data is protected and respected at all times.All Cookies used by and on Our Sites are used in accordance with current Cookie Law.Certain features of Our Sites depend on Cookies to function. Cookie Law deems these Cookies to be “strictly necessary”. These Cookies are shown in the table below. Your consent will not be sought to place these Cookies, but it is still important that you are aware of them. You may still block these Cookies by changing your internet browser’s settings as detailed below, but please be aware that Our Sites may not work properly if you do so. Our Sites use analytics services. Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyse anonymous usage information, enabling us to better understand how Our Sites are used. This, in turn, enables us to improve Our Sites and the products and services offered through it.The analytics service(s) used by Our Sites use(s) Cookies to gather the required information. You do not have to allow us to use these Cookies, however whilst our use of them does not pose any risk to your privacy or your safe use of Our Sites, it does enable us to continually improve Our Sites, making it a better and more useful experience for you.In addition to the controls that we provide, you can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. Most internet browsers also enable you to choose whether you wish to disable all Cookies or only third-party Cookies. By default, most internet browsers accept Cookies, but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet browser or the documentation that came with your device.You can choose to delete Cookies on your computer or device at any time, however you may lose any information that enables you to access Our Site more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, login and personalisation settings.It is recommended that you keep your internet browser and operating system up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser and manufacturer of your computer or device if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings.15. How Do I Contact You?To contact us about anything to do with your personal data and data protection, including to make a subject access request, please use the following details:Email address: GDPR (at) dict8.com.Telephone number: 0800 1218105.Postal Address: DICT8 Limited, 1st Floor, 1a St Mary Abbots Place, London W8 6LS.16. Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. This may be necessary, for example, if the law changes, or if we change our business in a way that affects personal data protection.Any changes will be immediately posted on Our Sites and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy on your first use of Our Site following the alterations. We recommend that you check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.
Back to Top
DICT8, 1A Saint Mary Abbot's Place, London, England, W8 6LS, United Kingdom0800 121 8105
©2019 DICT8 Ltd | Legal information | Privacy policy | Terms & conditions
